{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","address":"5546 McGraw St","zipcode":"4821","owner":"Jesus Rios","licenseNumber":"221019","licenseType":"Mobile Food Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/22/2017","establishmentType":"LHD - Mobile Food Establishmen","establishmentStatus":"Plan Review","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"395.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000E4BD0483D8C854C0983E4877192B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44693","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","inspectionDate":"2018-10-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"2","pfcount":"6","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"8","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Pest(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Present in facility","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove pests from facility."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"3-307.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination that may result from a factor or source not specified under Subparts 3-301 - 3-306.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not protected","subProblem":"From contamination","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Protect against contamination"},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"","location":"COMMISSARY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"2-401.11","violationDescription":"(A)    An EMPLOYEE shall eat, drink, or use any form of tobacco only in designated areas where the contamination of exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES; or other items needing protection can not result.\r\n(B)     A FOOD EMPLOYEE may drink from a closed BEVERAGE container if the container is handled to prevent contamination of:\r\n         (1)     The EMPLOYEE'S hands;\r\n         (2)     The container; and\r\n         (3)     Exposed FOOD; clean EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, and LINENS; and unwrapped SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Beverage container","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not covered","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-19T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep covered."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"5-203.11","violationDescription":"(A)  A HANDWASHING SINK or an approved automatic handwashing unit shall be provided as necessary for their convenient use by EMPLOYEES in areas specified and not fewer than the number of HANDWASHING SINKS required by LAW shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n(B)  If APPROVED, when FOOD exposure is limited and HANDWASHING SINKS are not conveniently available, such as in some mobile or TEMPORARY FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS or at some VENDING MACHINE LOCATIONS, EMPLOYEES may use chemically treated towelettes for handwashing.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing lavatories","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"44693","inspectionDate":"10/19/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"COMMISSARY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."}]},{"inspectionid":"39683","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","inspectionDate":"2017-08-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","inspectorid":"83","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39683","inspectionDate":"8/17/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39683","inspectionDate":"8/17/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-17T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water source/system to meet demand."},{"inspectionid":"39683","inspectionDate":"8/17/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Do not meet requirements of rule","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to meet requirements of rule."},{"inspectionid":"39683","inspectionDate":"8/17/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"4-202.16","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES shall be free of unnecessary ledges, projections, and crevices, and designed and constructed to allow easy cleaning and to facilitate maintenance.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"With ledges, projections, or crevices","subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"39683","inspectionDate":"8/17/2017","inspectionType":"Preopening/New","establishmentid":"51622525","name":"El Brasero","violationCode":"5-302.14","violationDescription":"If provided, a water tank vent shall terminate in a downward direction and shall be covered with: 16 mesh screen or equivalent when the vent is in a protected area or A protective filter when the vent is in an area that is not protected from windblown dirt and debris.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Mobile water tank vent","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"MOBILE UNIT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-08-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622525"}}